<ZT2Strings>

   <zoopedia_benthic>
      <entry>Benthic Biome</entry>
      <text>
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds" pady="15" padx="15">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
               <cell width="600">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/benthic_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
                  <p/>The benthic biome is the area of the ocean floor that is below the pelagic zone but does not include the very deepest parts of the ocean, which are known as the abyssal zone.
                  <p/>The bottom of the benthic biome consists of sand, silt, and dead organisms. Seaweed grows here, and certain animals and organism thrive in the  nutrient-rich environment, including bacteria, fungi, sponges, sea anemones, worms, sea stars, and bottom-feeding fish.
               </cell>
            </color>
         </cell>
      </text>
   </zoopedia_benthic>

   <zoopedia_coastal>
      <entry>Coastal Biome</entry>
      <text>
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds" pady="15" padx="15">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
               <cell width="600">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/coastal_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
                  <p/>The coastal biome, also known as the intertidal zone, is the area where the ocean meets the shore. It is sometimes submerged under water and sometimes exposed to the open air, so the animals and plants in this biome must adapt to either condition.
                  <p/>In the areas of land where the highest tides reach, there are only a few species of algae and mollusks. In those higher areas, there is a diverse array of algae and small animals, such as herbivorous snails, crabs, sea stars, and small fishes. At the bottom of the coastal biome, which is only exposed during the lowest tides, there are many invertebrates, fishes, and seaweed. All of these species must adapt to the constant volatility of moving sands. In coastal rocky cliff areas, which also qualify as coastal biomes, there are fewer life forms to support and they have a more consistent habitat.
   
               </cell>
            </color>
         </cell>
      </text>
   </zoopedia_coastal>

   <zoopedia_pelagic>
      <entry>Pelagic Biome</entry>
      <text>
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds" pady="15" padx="15">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
               <cell width="600">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/pelagic_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
                  <p/>The pelagic biome is the open ocean, far from any land. The pelagic biome is generally cold, though there is some variance in temperature due to thermal stratification as the warm and cold ocean currents constantly mix. Surface seaweeds thrive in the pelagic biome, as do many species of fish and some mammals, such as whales and dolphins.  
               </cell>
            </color>
         </cell>
      </text>
   </zoopedia_pelagic>
   
   <zoopedia_reef>
      <entry>Reef Biome</entry>
      <text>
         <cell pady="0" width="1000"/>
         <p/>
         <cell width="260"/>
         <cell width="640" bgimg="ui/zoopedia/topCellBg.dds" pady="15" padx="15">
            <color r="255" g="255" b="255">
               <cell width="600">
                  <img src="UI/zoopedia/biome/reef_zoopedia_biomebrush.dds" sx="0" sy="0" sw="256" sh="85"/>
                  <p/>The reef biome is a coastal and oceanic ecosystem renowned for its beautiful life forms and for providing one of the most biologically diverse habitats on Earth. A reef is a ridge or outcrop of rock in the sea that comes close to the surface. A coral reef is a reef that has been built largely or entirely by corals, tiny animals that live together in colonies. Over a period of hundreds or thousands of years, the limestone skeletons of coral build up with new corals growing on the skeletons of the dead ones. This physical structure, with its living surface of corals and other organisms, is a coral reef.   
               </cell>
            </color>
         </cell>
      </text>
   </zoopedia_reef>   

</ZT2Strings>
